Nitrna. I am Aika KINUI Aika, the scene on. I am Aika Kinui of Scene On, and I look forward to working with you.
Yes, so far we have worked together on three game projects, but this time I would like to talk about the event in which both of us will appear, Tokyo Night Land Vol. 3, V Sudani's Roses.
We did it!
The date is Wednesday, September 6, and the venue is Tokyo Kinema Club.
And the venue is Tokyo Kinema Club.
Performed by me, Nairimoto
Shinyan's Kinui Aika
Daikoku Yuzuki-chan from Team Shachi
Sakura Seta from Batten Shoujo-tai
Waka Yosumori from Inari Talk
Miyu Miyu from Uchitan
Riju Murahoshi of Ichi Family
Ibuki Mita of Crown Pop
MORI Kurumi
Mai-chan of Haru
Kana-chan of Haru and former male actor of Takarazuka, now an idol and youtuber, Maya Ayaha will be performing!
Gorgeous!
It's my first time to perform at Yoruen Land, and I'm suddenly going in alone amongst all these great, great people.
I'm really anxious.
So, Lunapan, I think you were in the last show, how was it?
I was in Volume 2 for the first time, and there was a girl who was in Volume 1.
What was it like? It's hard to imagine, isn't it? It's not like today's festivals, where there are kids from all different units.
I didn't know what to expect, but there was a lot of singing and acting.
It was like singing and acting, and everyone just connected and talked and acted and went straight to the song.
Volume 2 was like that, so there were a lot of first-timers as well, so we started talking about what it would be like, and then it expanded into a lot of different things, and we got to know each other better.
So we can get to know each other. I saw on sns that everyone seemed to be getting along very well.
They seemed to be having a lot of fun.
They were taking pictures after practice,
I saw their tweets about what they had done,
I was a little relieved,
I felt a little relieved,
But then I thought, "I still can't catch up with them,
What if they get mad at me?
I was a little scared,
But we're all in this together, right?
Yes, we are together.
If you need help, I can come to you.
You can come to us if you need help. Please let me know if you need help. I'm quite shy myself, but all the girls at STAPLA are friendly and kind.
Last time, Hanae from Kyushu Girls' Bath was on the stage for the first time, and when we were eating lunch together on the day, she said she was going to be bullied at first.
She said she thought she was going to be bullied at first, but then she said she was glad that everyone was nice to her,
I was glad that they thought I was kind. We all thought so. Then everyone is kind.
I remember that towards the end of the concert, I felt sad to say goodbye while singing, and I was almost crying,
But it was quite short, so there might have been some scars. So it's all right then.
Then, I'll be relieved. By the way, there may be a play, and if I tell them about the role I want to play, they may let me play it.
But I have never really played that role. Have you ever?
I don't really play in front of an audience either. I don't think so.
But since I've never acted before, I don't know what kind of person I can be.
I don't know what kind of person I can be. So I might not be able to act at all.
But I think the role of the madam you just played is a good one.
I don't have it with me! I'm too embarrassed!
That's true. I think the role of madam is great.
But you can wear various costumes for the role.
So, Madame...
Maybe you can wear a madam costume too.
Certainly something very fluffy,
Maybe, you know, gorgeous.
Maybe she can wear something like a gorgeous person.
I might be able to wear it.
Then please play the role of madam.
I'm not sure what the story will be like.
But it's a bit of a nightmare.But it's just like Uguisu.
Because it's a rose in the manner of Uguisunashi.
Like a rose.
It might work.
Then, we'll be the madam's friends.
Two of us as madam.
We'll both be Madame's mavs.
Mab.
So, we'll wear fur fur.
Wearing fur fur.
Singing.
Please.
I don't know, I was just wondering what this story would be like.
Really?
It's hard to imagine.
But, you know, we could sing a song or something,
Two people...or five,
We can sing with two people, or with five people,
I'd like to try and sing a lot of songs,
With someone else.
Cover songs, right?
Cover songs.
What kind of songs did you sing last time?
Last time it was famous songs that were popular in the past,
And the last time it was famous songs that were popular in the past, and also songs that are popular nowadays,
I think it was a famous song that the audience could enjoy,
I wonder.
I was covering a song like "Blue Mystery" by Smap.
A very famous song?
Yes, yes, yes.
I thought I saw a lot of idol songs.
But there were also a lot of songs by idols,
AKB48's Mever, for example,
Yes, quite a lot,
Yes, it's hard to get everyone to sing along.
It was hard work and lessons.
I was with Kaon-chan the other day,
I was in a one-man loincloth show with Kaon-chan the other day,
The audience has started today.
What should I do? I might not be able to keep up with them.
I don't know if I can keep up with them,
I thought it was like that,
It was different from what I imagined, in a good way,
I heard that there was singing and dancing.
So, the new sound is pretty good,
It's not so much idol-like,
We have a pretty cool concept,
We have never performed a royal idol song like AKB's. We are all working together on that kind of thing,
We are all working together on that kind of thing.
We are all working together to make it happen.
It's not so easy to be a part of the staff,
The genre of music we perform differs from unit to unit,
There are girls who say they are happy to wear these costumes and dance these cute dances,
There are girls who say they are happy to wear these costumes and dance these cute dances, and there are girls who say they are happy to wear cool costumes.
I want to try something cute.
Idols.
So, an idol and a madam.
I can't imagine. It's too much of a combination.
I wonder if it's okay. I want to do an idol and a madam.
An idol and a madam.Idol and madam.
With me.
I see.
Can we have an idol and a madam?
But, what was it again? Rumpin-chan was good as the Demon King.
Wait, as the Demon King?
The Demon King. I don't know what the story will be like.
You're right. That's true.
It's a story, isn't it?
Yes, it's a story. All of it.
Then, we have to get the Demon King and Madame out too.
I wonder what kind of story it will be.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
Please do.
For more information about Tokyo Yakan Land Vol. 3,
please visit the official Twitter of Yakan and Idol.
This is famous. They don't usually have it when they run out of drinks.
Today, they prepared it specially for us.
Shall we have a drink?
Cheers!
How's it going? It's good.
Yum!
What is it? By the way.
This is Coca-Cola.
My favorite.
Oh, great. I was just listening.
When I was getting my makeup done in the back,
I heard her say that she really likes Coke.
I thought it might have something in common.
I was talking about that too. What's that?
I'm drinking Red Bull.
You'd think it was beer, wouldn't you?
You think it's alcohol.
Don't worry. It's Red Bull.
I love Red Bull.
What is a stage drink?
Red Bull.
What do you mean? Every time?
Every time.
Why?
Because it gets me excited.
Every time?
Every live performance.
I saw that you drank Red Bull during rehearsal for the show.
Do you drink water?
I don't drink water.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Have you been to the hospital?
I don't know, but at festivals, there's always a short trip with one bottle.
If it's a one-man dive or something, I'll drink like 500 ml, 250 or 250.
And then you get thirsty.
Why do you drink when you get thirsty? I don't understand.
I don't know if it's good for your throat.
But my doctor said I could drink whatever I wanted.
I was like, "I'll have a Red Bull.
So it's okay then.
Do you have to drink soda?
Some people can't drink soda before or after a live performance.
I'm fine with the members I don't have in mind.No problem with members who don't have any idea.
Sure, I'm sure. I don't think they all drink juice or carbonated beverages.
It makes my stomach feel a little queasy or something.
I don't mind carbonated drinks at all.
What?
But you probably drink Coke all the time.
Yes, I do.
I think I can handle even water.
Because it's carbonated.
I'd be in big trouble if I used a stage drink.
What are you having?
Water.
When I have a long one-man show, I have Red Bull, milk tea, and tea.
What? Wait. I'm scared. Wait, wait, wait.
I've never met someone like that before.
With a voice.
I took a sip of Red Bull.
I met a guy who looked like he was from a drink bar.
Wait. Can fans see that?
I can see you. I can see you.
They're standing in line?
It's funny. Who is it?
They switch them around at festivals and stuff.
That's good. It's a thing.
The staff puts Red Bull on the table at that time.
Oh, wow.
I've heard that the previous staff gives them sensitivity.
Red Bull again today.
When you put the tea on the table...
Not Red Bull today?
No, it's not.
I've been told.
I thought so.
It's funny.
The fans recognize it.
It's Red Bull.
I think the fans are going to be worried.
I don't know.
Yes, they are.
Really?
I'm worried too.
You're worried about me?
Really. I am.
I'm fine.
I'm totally fine.
I'm really scared.
Please keep it to a minimum.
My eyes are getting so cancerous.
No more than two a day.
That's a lot. That's a lot, too.
I like cola.
I love cola.
Coke is delicious.
Then let's make the next stage drink Coke.
Let's make it Coke and Red Bull.
I'll do that too.
But the manager said no.
Oh, no.
But he said it's okay for the night time.
I'll only drink Coke and Red Bull at night.I would like to go with Coke and Red Bull only on nighttime days.
Lastly, please give a message to those who have watched this program one by one.
I'll start with a commemorative love song from Scene On, thank you for watching today.
I know this may seem like a strange trend, but this is the first time I've had the opportunity to talk with Rumpan-chan.
I've learned a lot of things through this project, this game project, and this talk.
I've learned a lot of things through this project, the game project, and now this conversation, and I feel like we've become good friends in a new way.
I hope that we will have another chance to meet again at another event or another night, even after this event is over.
I hope that we can get to know each other even better and that our fans will recognize Red Bull and the KORAHUMAN as well, so that this program will reach everyone's eyes, hands, and body.
I hope that this program will reach everyone's eyes, hands, and body like Red Bull.
Thank you very much for watching until the end.
I'm so glad that I was able to talk to you and play games with you and get to know you before I appeared on Yoruen Land today.
I'm going to try my best to be funny and cute and introduce Aikaman to everyone at the nighttime land and I'm going to enjoy my lessons with everyone.
Please come and visit us at Nighttime Land!